MBULELO PANI

• Junior Web Developer •

ABOUT ME

I am a junior web developer, based in Cape Town. I have experience in planning, testing and maintaining websites. I've also gained experience in working alone, as well as in studying and working within a team. My passion lies in designing the functionality of neat and interactive websites.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Full names - Mbulelo Pani

Gender - Male

Date of birth - 29/08/1997

Region - Cape Town, Western Cape

Nationality - South African

Email - Mbulelopani09@gmail.com

Phone - 073 703 6422

Profile - mbulelo20.github.io/my-portfolio2

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2020 - present LC Studio

Web Developer InternBackend developmentCode testing and cleanup

• Frontend testing

Oct, 2019 - Jan 2020 Sage Futuremakers Foundation

Volunteer facilitator (part time)

- Assist facilitator in introducing programming youngsters
- Plan lessons
- Assist in recruiting potential students from the townships

Jan 2020 (3 weeks) Old Mutual

Job Shadowing

Shadowed project manager, robotics developers

EDUCATION

Feb- Aug, 2020 • Lifechoices Academy

- Course: Fullstack Web Development, Lifeskills

June - Nov, 2019 • Melisizwe Computer Lab Project

- Course: Introduction to Programming

- Certificate: NQ6

2016 - Dec, 2018 • Northlink College

- Course: Logical Systems, Electrical Engineering

- Certificate: N4

2011 - 2015 • Sizimisele Technical High School

- Course : Electrical Engineering

- Certificate : Matric

SKILLS

Frontend design	Frameworks	Soft skills
HTML, CSS	MongoDB	Teamwork
•		Accountability
Javascript	MySQL	Open-mindedness
Python	ExpressJS	Learning
Responsive design	NodeJS	Critical thinking
		Time management
	React, VueJS, Angular	

ACTIVITIES

Interests	Hobbies	Volunteering
Robotics	Web design	Organization: Harare CAN Foundation
Machine Learning	Reading	Duration: Aug - Dec, 2020
Software design	Meditation	Tasks: deliver food parcels to poverty
Physics	Gaming	stricken areas around Harare, Khayelitsha.
	Circuit building	

REFERENCES

Khanya Qongqo

NGO: Harare CAN Foundation

Position: Marketer/manager

Contact: Qongqokhanya@gmail.com

Gift Khangamwa

NGO: Sage Future makers Foundation

Position: Facilitator

Contact: Gift@melisizwe.co.za